<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-10-25T22:47:11-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Startup Business Models</title><subtitle>Business Canvases of 1000+ companies</subtitle><entry><title type="html">zuora</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/zuora/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="zuora" /><published>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/zuora</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/zuora/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;businessmodel-of-zuora&quot;&gt;Businessmodel of Zuora&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-segments&quot;&gt;Customer Segments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zuora has a niche market business model, with a specialized customer segment. The company targets its offerings at firms that want to create subscription-based models or manage their existing ones. While it serves all industries, its customers are mostly in healthcare, education, and communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;value-proposition&quot;&gt;Value Proposition&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zuora offers three primary value propositions: convenience, performance, and brand/status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company offers convenience by providing an end-to-end solution. Its software handles all aspects of subscription management, from commerce to billing to finance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company has demonstrated strong performance through positive outcomes for clients. Specific examples include the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dell used Zuora’s solution to design an award-winning subscription experience and reduce new acquisition deployment time from over a year to six months&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reed Business Information used Zuora’s solution to to increase subscription revenues by more than 10% by optimizing pricing and upsells, as well as reducing churn&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mindvalley used Zuora’s solution to enhance the efficiency of billing processes and increase recurring revenes by approximately 25%&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Informatica used Zuora’s solution to increase its customer renewal rate to 95%&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Marketo used Zuora’s solution to increase its revenues by 5,000 percent
 The company has established a strong brand as a result of its performance. It has amassed over 700 customers. Also, it has received positive coverage in high-profile publications, including &lt;em&gt;Fortune, Forbes, *the *Wall Street Journal&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;TechCrunch&lt;/em&gt;. Lastly, it has won many honors, including placement on the CNBC Disruptor List (2014), recognition as an OnDemand Top 100 Company (2013) and “Company of the Year“ from AlwaysOn (2012), and listing on the FASTech 50 by VentureWire (2011).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;channels&quot;&gt;Channels&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zuora’s main channel is its direct sales team; it also acquires customers through its website. The company promotes its offering through its social media pages and attendance of conferences and other networking events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-relationships&quot;&gt;Customer Relationships&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zuora’s customer relationship is primarily of a self-service nature. Customers utilize the service through the main platform while having limited interaction with employees. The company’s website features a ”Content Library” that includes several self-help resources, including white papers, reports, eBooks, videos, demos, webinars, and keynotes. The website also offers platform status updates, access to a monthly newsletter, and answers to frequently asked questions. Furthermore, it provides 80 hours of self-paced and virtual instructor-led classes through “Zuora University“.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite this orientation, there is a personal assistance component in the form of phone support and a community element in the form of a forum where customers can obtain assistance from peers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-activities&quot;&gt;Key Activities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zuora’s business model entails designing software solutions and maintaining and updating its software platform for its customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-partners&quot;&gt;Key Partners&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zuora has the following types of partners:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Global System Integrators – Partners include Accenture, PwC, and Capgemini&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Accounting Partners – Partners include NetSuite, QuickBooks, SAGE, Workday, and Intaact&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Payment Providers – Partners include Chase Paymentech, FirstData, BlueSnap, and Cielo&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CRM and Sales Solutions – Partners include Salesforce.com, Sertifi, and Xactly&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Integration Providers – Partners include Dell Boomi, Flexera, Informatica, and MuleSoft
 ### Key Resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zuora’s main resource is its proprietary software platform, which serves over 700 customers. It also depends on its human resources in the form of instructors and service personnel to provide training and customer support. Lastly, as a relatively new startup it has relied heavily on funding from outside parties, raising $242.5 million from 17 investors as of March 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;cost-structure&quot;&gt;Cost Structure&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zuora has a cost-driven structure, aiming to minimize expenses through significant automation and low-price value propositions. Its biggest cost driver is likely marketing and sales expenses, a fixed cost. Other major drivers are in the areas of customer support/operations, also fixed costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;revenue-streams&quot;&gt;Revenue Streams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zuora has three revenue streams. It charges a one-time set-up fee for first time customers. Once they have signed up, it utilizes a revenue-share model in which it charges 2-3% of the total amount clients invoice each month. Lastly, it charges an overage fee usage outside of set parameters.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Businessmodel of Zuora</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">zozi</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/zozi/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="zozi" /><published>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/zozi</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/zozi/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;businessmodel-of-zozi&quot;&gt;Businessmodel of ZOZI&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-segments&quot;&gt;Customer Segments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zozi’s two-pronged business model targets different customer segments. Its direct consumer-facing website serves general consumers that are seeking new activities, events and excursions in which to take part.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Company’s offerings cater to a wide range of interests – including adventure trips, extreme sports, food and drink experiences, classes, spa breaks and sightseeing tours – with products appropriate for all ages and at a variety of differing price points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the Company provides access to experiences across the world, its principal market remains the US, which accounts for the vast majority of the Company’s website traffic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zozi’s business software solutions serve a number of small and medium-sized local tour operators, event organisers, equipment rental providers and activity centres.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;value-propositions&quot;&gt;Value Propositions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zozi’s principal value to consumers is that it allows them to browse and book a broad variety of activities and experiences across a range of locations, both local and international, from one single place. The website’s searchable catalogue is easy to access and navigate, and provides access to deals that are not available elsewhere, through its network of supplier partners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zozi also sets itself apart from competitors by offering high-end experiences and insights provided by experts, including extreme sports practitioners and explorers, through its Zozi Gurus program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For business customers, Zozi’s greatest value is its software, which enables tour companies to manage online reservations, rentals and payments from one platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The platform is accessible via desktop and mobile browsers and through mobile apps, allowing customers to manage its bookings from anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;channels&quot;&gt;Channels&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Zozi marketplace can be accessed by consumers through its mobile and desktop websites at www.zozi.com, where users can make bookings and reservations. The Company’s catalogue of tours and experiences can also be accessed via its network of affiliate partners, which account for much of the Zozi website’s traffic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zozi’s business software can be purchased and accessed through the Company website. Zozi also provides iOS and Android apps that enable its business customers to view bookings and rentals and accept online payments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-relationships&quot;&gt;Customer Relationships&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zozi’s online marketplace operates on a self-service basis, providing a fully searchable catalogue of tours and experiences, categorised by location, style, and social group Consumers are able to make purchases and bookings through the website directly, with no interaction with Zozi representatives. Consumers also have access to reviews and advice contributed by members of the Zozi Guru team, which comprises extreme sports practitioners, explorers and photographers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Business customers are able to organise software trials and demos through the Zozi website, with sales being completed via the Company’s sales team. Zozi’s business customers receive support through the website’s Help Centre, which includes common questions, user tutorials and troubleshooting guides. Zozi also hosts a blog through which it publishes business tips for tour, operators and event organisers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both consumer and business customers can stay up to date with Zozi’s activities through its Facebook, Twitter and Instagram accounts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-activities&quot;&gt;Key Activities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zozi provides online reservation, payment, and customer management software solutions to tour and activity businesses, primarily across the US but also internationally, and operates an online marketplace of tours, activities and experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Company’s flagship Zozi Advance software product serves as a full-service online booking system, allowing tour operators to manage their schedules, reservations, rentals and online payments from one place, with mobile access to the system available via its iOS and Android apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its backend software also enables customers to manage inventory and customer communications and a mobile application to run business on the go and take mobile payments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Company also manages an affiliate marketing network and provides reviews and advice through its team of Zozi Gurus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-partners&quot;&gt;Key Partners&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zozi’s key partners are its tour and experience suppliers, social media applications, affiliates and technology companies. The Company’s consumer-facing marketplace sells tours, experiences and access to attractions provided by a network of suppliers, primarily comprising local or regional tour operators, travel agencies, museums, activity centres, event organisers, workshops, restaurants and bars. This includes local operators around the US and abroad, including Xperience Adventures, Urban Adventures, Discover Hawaii Tours, Getaway Halong Spa, Ecuador Pure Life and Dot Red.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zozi also operates an affiliate marketing program, through which affiliate partners can earn commissions through referrals. It has in particular worked closely with affiliate marketing agency Clique. The Company has also partnered with location-based search and discovery platform Foursquare and group messaging application GroupMe, with which it has integrated functionality. F&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;oursquare now makes Zozi local daily deals viewable through its app, and GroupMe has collaborated with Zozi through its GroupMe Experiences program which offers deals on local events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-resources&quot;&gt;Key Resources&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zozi’s key resources are its software products, its IT infrastructure, its supplier partners and its personnel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Company’s consumer revenue model depends on the quality of its catalogue and the discounts offered by its suppliers, while the Company’s business revenue depends on the reliability and efficiency of its software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;cost-structure&quot;&gt;Cost Structure&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zozi’s principal costs relate to the development of its software products, maintenance of its IT infrastructure and retention of its personnel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Company must also pay commissions to its affiliate marketing partners which drive much of the Zozi website’s traffic, and pay rental and utility fees for its offices in San Francisco, New York and Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;revenue-streams&quot;&gt;Revenue Streams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zozi generates revenue through the sale of software products and services to businesses and via the sale of activities and tours directly to consumers. This revenue is estimated to be as much as $117 million per year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Company’s flagship Zozi Advance platform, which enables customers to manage their business’ booking system, communications and online payments from one place, is available on a subscription basis starting at $39 per month. Zozi also takes a 10% commission on sales made through its online tour and activity marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Previously, the Company generated additional revenue through the sale of travel and adventure equipment and clothing, it, however, appears to have discontinue this revenue stream.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Businessmodel of ZOZI</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">zopa</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/zopa/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="zopa" /><published>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/zopa</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/zopa/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;businessmodel-of-zopa&quot;&gt;Businessmodel of Zopa&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-segments&quot;&gt;Customer Segments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zopa has a multi-sided business model, with two interdependent customer segments that are both needed in order to operate:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Borrowers: Consumers who wish to obtain loans outside of traditional sources such as banks.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lenders: Individuals seeking better returns on their investment money from borrowers.
 ### Value Proposition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zopa offers six primary value propositions: accessibility, convenience, cost reduction, risk reduction, performance, and brand/status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company creates accessibility by enabling borrowers who are normally seen as a risk by banks to obtain personal loans from other individuals who are able and willing to lend them money. Applicants can borrow up to £25,000, and loans are available for a wide variety of purposes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company offers convenience to borrowers by providing flexible terms. Loans are available over a period of one to five years. In addition, applicants can view tailored loan rates in just three minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company reduces costs by providing loans at lower rates than regular banks – they range from 5.9% to 12%. Moreover, it does not charge early repayment fees. Customers can repay as soon as they like or make extra payments without penalty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company reduces risk for borrowers by ensuring that loan quotes do not impact applicants’ credit scores. It reduces risk for lenders by performing credit and identity checks on borrowers and utilizing collections agencies to contact borrowers about missed payments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company has demonstrated strong performance. It has lent £1.49 billion from more than 63,000 lenders to over 150,000 consumers since 2005. It lends over £2 million a day on average, with the average loan amount equaling £7,300. For lenders, it provides an average return of 6.2% (after fees and before bad debts). Investors have earned millions of pounds in interest since the service began.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company has established a powerful brand as a result of its popularity. It bills itself as Europe’s largest and the world’s oldest peer-to-peer lending service. It has been voted the “Most Trusted Loan Provider” by the Moneywise Customer Service Awards every year from 2010 to 2015. Other honors it has received include recognition as MoneySuperMarket’s “Best Personal Loans Provider” from 2014 to 2016, one of the UK’s “Most Disruptive Tech Companies” by Tech City Future Fifty, and “Growing Business of the Year” in 2015 by Real Business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;channels&quot;&gt;Channels&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zopa’s main channel is its website, through which it obtains most customers. The company promotes its offering through its social media pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-relationships&quot;&gt;Customer Relationships&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zopa’s customer relationship is primarily of a self-service, automated nature. Customers utilize the service through the main platform while having limited interaction with employees. The company’s website includes case studies and detailed answers to frequently asked questions. That said, there is a personal assistance component in the form of phone and e-mail support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-activities&quot;&gt;Key Activities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zopa’s business model entails maintaining a robust common platform between two parties:  borrowers and lenders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-partners&quot;&gt;Key Partners&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zopa actively invites other entities to join it in partnership – specifically those who share its goal of “making money simple and fair.” Organizations of interest include affiliates, banks, brokers, and online retailers. The company currently maintains the following partnerships:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Metro Bank – Lends money to consumers on the Zopa platform, expanding its reach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Uber – Obtains loans from Zopa for Uber drivers who want to buy their cars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unshackled – Receives financing from Zopa for handset sales in its mobile phone marketplace; it integrates Zopa’s technology into its website through the company’s Partner API, allowing customers to spread out handset payments over two years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SalaryFinance – Obtains loans for its employees that can be repaid through salary deductions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-resources&quot;&gt;Key Resources&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zopa’s main resource is its proprietary software platform, which serves more than 63,000 lenders. It depends on its engineering employees to maintain and update the platform and customer service staff to provide support.  Lastly, as a startup it has relied heavily on funding from outside parties, raising $56.63 million from nine investors as of January 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;cost-structure&quot;&gt;Cost Structure&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zopa has a cost-driven structure, aiming to minimize expenses through significant automation and low-price value propositions. Its biggest cost driver is likely transaction expenses, a fixed cost. Other major drivers are in the areas of customer support/operations and administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;revenue-streams&quot;&gt;Revenue Streams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zopa has one revenue stream: transaction fees. These include a fee for borrowers and an annual fee of 1% for lenders.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Businessmodel of Zopa</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">zoom-video-communications</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/zoom-video-communications/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="zoom-video-communications" /><published>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/zoom-video-communications</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/zoom-video-communications/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;businessmodel-of-zoom-video-communications&quot;&gt;Businessmodel of Zoom Video Communications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-segments&quot;&gt;Customer Segments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zoom has a mass market business model, with no significant differentiation between customer segments. The company targets organizations of all industries and sizes that seek videoconferencing solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;value-proposition&quot;&gt;Value Proposition&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zoom offers three primary value propositions: accessibility, performance, and brand/status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company’s solution creates accessibility by providing a wide variety of options. It offers video conferencing, group messaging, simple online meetings, and a software-defined conference room feature. Furthermore, it can be used on the Windows, Linux, Mac, iOS, Blackberry, Android, and Zoom Rooms systems, as well as H.323/SIP room systems such as Cisco Tandberg and Polycom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company’s solution has demonstrated strong performance through tangible results for clients. High-profile examples of positive outcomes include the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Trend Micro used Zoom’s solution to simplify its communication platforms, increasing its productivity by 20-39% when compared with its previous systems&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Global logistics company JAS used Zoom’s solution to increase its capacity for large meetings to as many as 100 two-way video participants, particularly useful for training sessions&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Focus Investment Banking used Zoom’s solution to host a wide variety of meetings, saving at least $25,000 a year in air travel while increasing brand exposure&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Access Physicians used Zoom’s solution to expand care access, resulting in reductions in critical care and emergency room visits, translating to significant savings for patients and its facilities&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;BAYADA Home Health Care used Zoom’s solution for its 300 offices, resulting in increased efficiency, higher adoption rates, and lower total cost of ownership
 Zoom’s impressive performance has led to strong approval from customers. The company had a third party conduct a survey of its clients that showed a Net Promoter Score of 69, as well as these results:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;94% of respondents said Zoom’s solution is easier to use than that of the competition&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;92% of respondents said Zoom’s solution is of a higher quality than that of the competition&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;87% of respondents said Zoom’s solution is more reliable than that of the competition&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;75% of respondents said Zoom’s solution has enhanced their productivity by at least 40%
 The company has established a strong brand as a result of its performance. It serves over 300,000 companies, including prominent clients such as Arista, UCLA, and SolarCity. It has also won many honors, including recognition as one of Trust Radius’s Top Rated Web Conferencing Software solutions (2016), Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan‘s Entrepreneurial Company of the Year (2016), an Emergence Award from Emergence Capital (2015), and recognition as a Gartner Cool Vendor (2014).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;channels&quot;&gt;Channels&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zoom’s main channel is its website, through which new customers sign up for an account; however, it also maintains a direct sales team. The company promotes its offering through its social media pages, live demos, webinars, and participation in symposiums and conferences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-relationships&quot;&gt;Customer Relationships&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zoom’s customer relationship is primarily of a self-service nature. Customers utilize the service through the main platform while having limited interaction with employees. The company’s website features self-help resources such as online training and answers to frequently asked questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That said there is a personal assistance component in the form of phone and e-mail support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-activities&quot;&gt;Key Activities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zoom’s business model entails designing/developing its software and maintaining/updating its software-as-a-service platform for customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-partners&quot;&gt;Key Partners&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zoom maintains the following types of partnerships:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Integration Partners - The company works with firms that integrate their offerings into its product for an enhanced solution. Integration categories and some of their specific partners are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Content Sharing – Microsoft (One Drive), Google Drive, Box, Dropbox&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Scheduling &amp;amp; Starting Meetings – Slack, Salesforce, Skype, Firefox, Microsoft (Outlook)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Unified Login – Facebook, Google, Centrify, Okta, Microsoft (Active Directory)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Marketing/Process Automation – Marketo, Zapier, Pardot, Infusionsoft&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Room Collaboration – Intel Unite, Kubi
 Technology Partners - The company works with firms that pair their offerings with its solution to produce complementary benefits. Partner types are technology vendors, application providers, and manufacturers. Specific partners include Altia Systems, Biscotti, CVI Gear, HoverCam, InFocus, Logitech, OpenSignal, Phoenix Audio Technologies, Revolve Robotics, Vaddio, and Yealink.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Refer-A-Friend - The company invites customers to refer its solution to their friends and associates. Referrals that lead to a purchase result in commissions for the customer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reseller Partners – The company works with firms that promote and sell its products to their customers in order to extend its reach. Partner types are value-added resellers and systems integrators with specializations in AV Technology and Video Collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Partners receive the following benefits:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Permission to use the Zoom logo&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Co-selling opportunities with Zoom’s salesforce&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Access to competitive incentive programs&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Joint demand-generation activities&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Continuous interoperability testing&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Frequent market and product updates
 ### Key Resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zoom’s main resources are its human resources, who include the engineering employees that design its software and maintain its platform, the sales staff that promote it, and the customer service staff that provide support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a relatively new startup it has relied heavily on funding from outside parties, raising $45.5 million from 15 investors as of February 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;cost-structure&quot;&gt;Cost Structure&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zoom has a cost-driven structure, aiming to minimize expenses through significant automation and low-price value propositions. Its biggest cost driver is likely sales/marketing, a fixed expense. Other major drivers are in the areas of customer support/operations and administration, both fixed costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;revenue-streams&quot;&gt;Revenue Streams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zoom has one revenue stream: the subscription fees it charges for monthly access to its software platform. Subscription plans are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Basic – Free&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pro - $14.99 per month per host&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Business - $19.99 per month per host (minimum of 10 hosts)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Enterprise – Sales staff must be contacted for price quotes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Businessmodel of Zoom Video Communications</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">ziprecruiter</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/ziprecruiter/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="ziprecruiter" /><published>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/ziprecruiter</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/ziprecruiter/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;businessmodel-of-ziprecruiter&quot;&gt;Businessmodel of ZipRecruiter&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-segments&quot;&gt;Customer Segments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ziprecruiter provide recruitment and job search services to a range of individual and commercial customers. The Company’s customers can be organised broadly into two core categories:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Individuals, comprising jobseekers of all ages and professions, to whom its provides an accessible and flexible source of job seeking tools; and&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Commercial Entities, comprising a range of commercial enterprises across multiple sectors, to which the Company provides services and tools to assist in the recruitment process.
 Ziprecruiter lists a number of its individual and commercial clients on its website. The Company’s enterprise customers include The Sigma Law Group, Applebee’s, Safety Management Group, Matrix Medical Network, Lighthouse Management Group, and MONZINGO.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ziprecruiter serves an extensive customer base in its native US, as well as a significant customer base in the UK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;value-propositions&quot;&gt;Value Propositions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ziprecruiter provides value to its clients in the following ways:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Its brand strength and industry standing, with the Company established as a leading portal for jobseekers and commercial recruiters, having a well-known and well-respected brand name within the industry;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Its accessibility and flexibility, with the Company offering a range of services through its online portal and mobile application that can be accessed quickly and easily by users from anywhere and at any time;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Its commitment to innovation, with the Company committed to developing and implementing new and innovative solutions, ensuring that its services are at the cutting edge of the industry;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Its large user base, with the Company serving providing customers with an extensive catalogue of job opportunities and managing the profiles of more than 7 million active job seekers for commercial recruiters; and&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Its international reach, with the Company serving an extensive domestic customer base in the US, as well as a significant customer base in the UK.
 ### Channels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ziprecruiter operates a website at ww.ziprecruiter.com, through which it provides information on its various services, solutions, and activities. The Company’s website also doubles as its job search and recruitment platform, with users able to log in to its online portal through the Ziprecruiter homepage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Company’s provides a range of tools and resources to customers directly through its online portal, through which users can search for jobs, browse CVs, and manage account details. Ziprecruiter also provide mobile applications that are available on iOS and Android devices that offer a similar set of functions and tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ziprecruiter offers support and services through dedicated sales and service teams organised by geographic regions, namely the UK and the US. These personnel operate out of the Company’s network of offices, primarily in the US. Ziprecruiter additionally operates an affiliate program through which it reaches customers. The Company’s affiliate partners seek to drive traffic to Ziprecruiter and generate business on its behalf.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-relationships&quot;&gt;Customer Relationships&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ziprecruiter operates on a primarily self-service basis through its online platform, which enable individual users and commercial users to access a range of tools and resources without interacting with members of the Company’s sales and service teams. Users are able to browse job listings, apply for jobs, search CVs, and manage account details completely independently. Ziprecruiter also has a sale and service team that is able to serve customers more personally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ziprecruiter offers ongoing support to its customers. Individual and commercial users are able to contact the company’s dedicated support personnel over the phone, via an online contact form, by email, or through an online chat service, through which they are provided tailored support and assistance. The Company also offers users a range of online resource, such as FAQs and guides.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, Ziprecruiter operates several social media accounts – including with Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn – through which the Company is able to publish company updates and interact directly with customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-activities&quot;&gt;Key Activities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ziprecruiter is a provides employment and recruitment services. The Company a range of solutions, including recruiting, hiring, job boards, job posting, web application, candidate screening, applicant tracking, and job alerts services, serving individual jobseekers and commercial recruiters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Company provides services primarily through its online jobs portal at www.ziprecruiter.com, through which customers can browse jobs and candidates, send applications and invites, and manage account details directly. Ziprecruiter serves an extensive customer base in the US, as well as in the UK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-partners&quot;&gt;Key Partners&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ziprecruiter works in close conjunction with a network of partner companies and organisations in the development and delivery of its services. These partners can be organised broadly into the following categories:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Supplier and Vendor Partners, comprising suppliers of services, equipment, and technologies that are utilised in the development and implementation of the Company’s services and solutions;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Software and Technology Partners, comprising software developers, including developers of applicant tracking systems, and technology companies that assist in the development and implementation of the Company’s various software offerings;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Publishing and Affiliate Partners, comprising a range of online companies and websites that assist in marketing the Company’s services and solutions, driving traffic to the Ziprecruiter website in return for commissions;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Distribution and Listing Partners, comprising various job board and job listing websites with which the Company collaborates to provide its users with access to an exhaustive list of jobs and candidates; and&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Strategic and Alliance Partners, comprising a range of companies across multiple sectors, with which the Company collaborates on arrange of projects, including in marketing, branding and development.
 Ziprecruiter has launched a number of partnerships in recent years. This includes a strategic partnership with Recruiterbox, a recruiting partnership with InfinityHR, and a software partnership with Greenhouse Software.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-resources&quot;&gt;Key Resources&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ziprecruiter’s key resources are its proprietary technologies and intellectual properties, its online platform and software offerings, its IT and communications infrastructure, its support channels, its partnerships, and its personnel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Searches of records published by the US Patent and Trademark Office identified no patent applications filed in the name of Ziprecruiter, either as applicant or assignee. Ziprecruiter additionally owns and or leases a number of physical properties that comprise its office and support centre network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;cost-structure&quot;&gt;Cost Structure&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ziprecruiter incurs costs in relation to the development of its technologies and solutions, the development and maintenance of its online platform, the maintenance of its IT and communications infrastructure, the management of its partnerships, the procurement of professional services, the implementation of marketing and advertising campaigns, and the retention of its personnel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;revenue-streams&quot;&gt;Revenue Streams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ziprecruiter generates revenue through the provision of various job search and recruitment services and solutions to individual jobseekers and commercial recruiters. The Company derives much of its revenue through the provision of paid services to commercial recruiters, including charging a small fee for posting job listings on its website. These Company’s premium offerings come in several pricing levels: Starter, Team, and Enterprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ziprecruiter remains a privately-owned company and as such is not obliged to publish its financial results online. Research did not identify any reference to the Company’s most recent revenue figures; reports from 2014, however, suggest that the Company generates annual revenue in excess of $50 million.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Businessmodel of ZipRecruiter</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">zillow</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/zillow/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="zillow" /><published>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/zillow</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/zillow/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;businessmodel-of-zillow&quot;&gt;Businessmodel of Zillow&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-segments&quot;&gt;Customer Segments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zillow has a multi-sided business model, with two interdependent customer segments that are both needed in order to operate:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Consumers: Individuals assess their home values, research home listings, and contact agents.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Real Estate Agents: Professionals advertise their services and connect with consumers.
 ### Value Proposition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zillow offers three primary value propositions: accessibility, customization, and brand/status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company offices one of the most comprehensive real estate databases on the market, covering the full cycle of home living, including buying, selling, renting, financing, and remodeling. The system has more than 110 million U.S. homes, and features a wide breadth of property facts, listing information, and purchase/sales data. Its vast size gives visitors access to more types of content than they would normally be able to get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The database gives customers a personalized experience. They can save home listings as “Favorites“ on both the website and the firm’s mobile app. They can also sign up for monthly e-mail updates on changes in these homes’ values, price changes, listing status, and other data. Users also have the option of creating “Saved Searches“ for a given zip code or neighborhood and obtaining daily e-mail updates on new homes listed for rent or sale, as well as price changes for already-listed homes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zillow’s brand name is powerful due to its success. Most of the website’s traffic come from direct look-ups rather than through general queries on search engines. In the quarter ended December 2015, site traffic rose to 123.7 million average monthly unique users, an increase of 61% compared to the quarter ended December 2014&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;channels&quot;&gt;Channels&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zillow’s main channel is its website, through which it markets and enables usage of its services. The company also engages in large-scale national TV advertising. Further, it has its staff of real estate industry experts provide commentary in national broadcast and print media outlets, as well as write blog posts and guest opinion pieces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, it communicates with customers through social media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-relationships&quot;&gt;Customer Relationships&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zillow’s customer relationship is primarily of a self-service, automated nature. Customers utilize the company’s database while having limited interaction with its employees. Also, its website has a detailed Help Center that provides answers to many potential questions and a forum for receiving assistance from other users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, there is also a personal assistance component as its website features contact information (addresses) for Zillow locations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-activities&quot;&gt;Key Activities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company’s business model involves maintaining a common platform between two parties: consumers and real estate agents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The platform consists of the main website and its suite of mobile real estate apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-partners&quot;&gt;Key Partners&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zillow maintains partnerships through the following programs:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Affiliate Program: This program recruits website owners with a real estate focus to promote the company on their platforms. Partners receiveaccess to a customized dashboard which they can use to monitor traffic to Zillow through their sites. The more visits, the more they get paid.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Zillow Pro for Brokers: Zillow makes companies establish a direct feed to Zillow; afterwards their logos and an outbound link to their websites are included on their listings, making it simple to for buyers and sellers to connect with them. Zillow puts the firms‘ listing agents first in buyers‘ contact options so they can start receiving leads right away.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Zillow Partnership Program (ZPP): This is an alliance between Zillow and MLS (a real estate property listings company) that improves listing accuracy and accessibility through a direct listings feed to Zillow. The collaboration gives buyers the latest information, gives sellers timely exposure for their homes, and provides agents with relevant outreach on properties.
 ### Key Resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zillow’s main resource is intellectual property – its proprietary algorithm that enables the calculation of home values (“Zestimates”). It has 18 patents covering techniques for this purpose. The company also relies heavily on its technology platform that provides customers with powerful online tools to carry out their customizable database searches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, its sales team is an important resource, marketing its services to consumers and real estate agents alike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;cost-structure&quot;&gt;Cost Structure&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zillow has a cost-driven structure. It tries to keep expenses low through heavy automation on its website. Its biggest cost driver is sales/marketing expenses, as it utilizes a variety of advertising channels. Other major drivers are technology/development and administrative expenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;revenue-streams&quot;&gt;Revenue Streams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zillow has two main revenue streams, which are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Subscription Revenue:  The company generates revenue from the sale of subscription packages that allow real estate and mortgage industry professionals to promote their services on its site.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Display Revenue:  The company obtains revenue from the sale of display advertising packages to companies of all kinds who desire to promote their brands on its website, its partner websites, and its mobile applications. The packages are sold on a cost per thousand impressions (“CPM”) or cost-per-click (“CPC”) basis, and pricing is based on ad positon and size.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Businessmodel of Zillow</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">zenefits</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/zenefits/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="zenefits" /><published>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/zenefits</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/zenefits/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;businessmodel-of-zenefits&quot;&gt;Businessmodel of Zenefits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-segments&quot;&gt;Customer Segments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zenefits has a multi-sided business model, with two interdependent customer segments that are both needed in order to operate:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Benefits Providers: Benefits providers offer the following programs through the system: health insurance, flexible spending accounts (e.g., FSAs and HSAs), workers’ compensation, COBRA, property &amp;amp; casualty insurance, life &amp;amp; disability insurance, 401K plans, and stock options.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;HR Departments: HR departments sign up for the system and use it to manage the various benefits programs for their employees, communicating relevant information as needed.
 ### Value Proposition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zenefits offers three primary value propositions: convenience, price, and cost reduction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company’s software simplifies the HR management process by enabling employers to work with HR service vendors/benefits providers through one party rather than through multiple brokers. It also makes the day-to-day processes involved with management easier by automating many of them (e.g., adding a new hire to payroll or removing a terminated worker from benefits) and integrating them into one interface. This saves time and increases productivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zenefits’ business model enables employers to use its system for free. This is a significant incentive for organizations to sign up, as they can use the money normally associated with paying brokers for other purposes. Finally, the company’s automation of most processes helps reduce ongoing expenses for companies, as HR staff members do not have to print or fax as many documents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;channels&quot;&gt;Channels&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zenefits’ main channel is its software platform, through which its customers carry out most of their tasks. However, it also operates through the mobile channel. Customers can utilize its mobile app, Zenefits People, which enables HR staff members to connect automatically to their Zenefits accounts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-relationships&quot;&gt;Customer Relationships&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zenefits’ customer relationship is primarily of a self-service, automated nature. Customers utilize the service through the main platform while having limited interaction with employees. The company has moved further and further in this direction – it has designed several new programs to automate previously manual tasks such as assisting employees with insurance enrollment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A prominent example of such software is Zenefits Payroll, released in late 2015. It takes information from other Zenefits systems and automatically runs payroll, saving HR from having to do things such as handle address changes or input time sheets. Emphasizing this strategy has enabled Zenefits to slow hiring in its customer service department, as there are not as many questions. This in turn has reduced employment costs. Despite this, it still offers live support to help staff when needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-activities&quot;&gt;Key Activities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zenefits’ key activities focus on platform management. The company’s business model entails maintaining a common platform between two parties: benefits providers and HR departments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-partners&quot;&gt;Key Partners&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zenefits encourages third-party developers to partner with the company by integrating their applications into the system for use by customers. It also actively partners with accountants, as it shares many of the same small business clients as that group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its program Zenefits for Accountants supports those who wish to give their clients HR and benefits resources, in addition to tax and payroll advice. Members have exclusive access to the Zenefits’ accountant partnership team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-resources&quot;&gt;Key Resources&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zenefits’ main resource is its proprietary software platform, which connects more than 1,000 carriers with more than 10,000 employers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also depends on its human resources to ensure customer satisfaction, namely its staff of 1,600 employees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, as a relatively new start-up it has relied heavily on funding from investors, raising $583.6 million from 30 companies as of May 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;cost-structure&quot;&gt;Cost Structure&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zenefits has a cost-driven structure, aiming to minimize expenses through significant automation and low-price value propositions. The company’s hiring slowdown is reflective of this reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;revenue-streams&quot;&gt;Revenue Streams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zenefits has two revenue streams. The company charges benefits providers a commission when customers purchase insurance through the platform. It claims that the fees are lower than those of most brokers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the money it earns from this set-up is enough to allow it to make the use of its system free for employers, as the fees add up quickly. Zenefits also offers optional paid features through its core HR platform, such as stock options administration; also, in certain cases usage may incur an implementation fee.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Businessmodel of Zenefits</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">zendesk</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/zendesk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="zendesk" /><published>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/zendesk</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/zendesk/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;businessmodel-of-zendesk&quot;&gt;Businessmodel of Zendesk&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-segments&quot;&gt;Customer Segments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zendesk targets customers from a wide variety of businesses, ranging from tiny startups to multinational corporations. As every business needs some level of customer support, every business is a potential customer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The range of Zendesk’s customer groups are defined by price, and the service delivered for such price. This enables customers to only pay what is necessary for the efficient running of their business and no more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;value-proposition&quot;&gt;Value Proposition&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zendesk aims to make customer service easier and more efficient. The unique customer service software is designed to open up conversations between businesses and their customers, bringing them closer together. Zendesk unifies various methods of communication, and streamlines their uses, ultimately making the customer service platform simpler and more intuitive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The product allows for companies to completely customize their software, strengthening their brand and reflecting individual businesses’ values. Zendesk has introduced innovative tools to help companies understand their customers’ needs, for example the introduction of the Net Promoter Score survey, and the Zendesk Benchmark, that allows businesses to compare their performance to others in a similar field. The software is also compatible with hundreds of well-established apps, allowing businesses to integrate their favorite tools into Zendesk. Innovation is key and so Zendesk frequently adds new services and features weekly, which are announced on its website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zendesk has a well-defined, visually pleasing brand that was developed with long-term customer satisfaction in mind. A strong focus is made on customer evangelism, in which loyal customers are identified, nurtured and then encouraged to stimulate conversations. Strong content marketing and a well-designed website ensure that customers are quickly engaged with Zendesk at the first point of contact. Zendesk has quickly received a reputation as one of the premier SaaS (Software-at-a-Service) companies, especially for a customer service platform, and as a brilliant example of a bootstrapped startup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;channels&quot;&gt;Channels&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zendesk uses one primary sales channel, which is its website. Via the website clients can purchase and upgrade various software packages. Direct sales support is also available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zendesk is marketed through numerous means including television adverts, print adverts, its website and social media platforms. Though the marketing team focus strongly on creating conversations between customers and providing positive customer experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-relationships&quot;&gt;Customer Relationships&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a software company dedicated to improving customer service experiences and strengthening the bonds between consumer and provider through communication, Zendesk strongly focuses on creating strong customer relationships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consistent support for clients, a clear and easy-to-use website, and comprehensive knowledgebase ensure that customers are rarely dissatisfied. An online community exists with open forums, frequently asked questions, product feedback channels, user-groups and discussions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technical support is available for the migration of data and in tailoring the Zendesk design for a more personalized customer experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-activities&quot;&gt;Key Activities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zendesk focuses on developing and providing software, tailored as a customer service platform. Due to the online nature of the product, manufacturing is not necessary, though continued support is available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-partners&quot;&gt;Key Partners&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zendesk relies on numerous partners to help guide and enhance clients’ Zendesk experience. Implementation of complex software can be difficult and so third-party businesses offer support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-resources&quot;&gt;Key Resources&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zendesk’s main resources are its Research and Development team, dedicated to improving current facilities and innovating new software, and Zendesk’s marketing efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Providing a non-physical product, Zendesk has to focus on innovation, service, support and marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;cost-structure&quot;&gt;Cost Structure&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zendesk has a value-driven cost structure, offering different degrees of the product for varying prices. The most restricted version of the product is the most affordable, and the most comprehensive version of the product is the most expensive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Major cost drivers include research, development, marketing and administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;revenue-streams&quot;&gt;Revenue Streams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zendesk’s main revenue stream is generated from the subscription revenue and licensing fees of its software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue was $208.8 million for the year ending December 31st, 2015. An increase of 64% over the prior year.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Businessmodel of Zendesk</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">zazzle</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/zazzle/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="zazzle" /><published>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/zazzle</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/zazzle/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;businessmodel-of-zazzle&quot;&gt;Businessmodel of Zazzle&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-segments&quot;&gt;Customer Segments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zazzle has a multi-sided business model, with two interdependent customer segments that are needed in order to operate:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Consumers – Individuals who design products on the website, either by using their own ideas or templates on the site produced by designers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Designers – Professionals and brands that produce designs/templates for consumers to use
 ### Value Proposition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zazzle offers five primary value propositions: customization, accessibility, convenience, cost reduction, and brand/status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company enables customization by allowing customers to personalize products. They can apply their own designs to items such as T-shirts or mugs or use existing templates provided by designers on the website. It also allows designers to personalize their website storefronts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company creates accessibility by providing a wide variety of options. Because it enables customers to have design input, they can create products that they cannot purchase elsewhere. These products are offered in several different categories, including Clothing &amp;amp; T-Shirts; Cards &amp;amp; Postage; Art &amp;amp; Posters; Home &amp;amp; Pets; Office; Electronics; Accessories; and Craft Supplies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company offers convenience by making life simpler for customers. After designing an item, customers can visualize exactly what it will look like in real life before making an order. Most products are shipped within 24 hours. This is possible because items are only manufactured after they are ordered, resulting in low inventory. In addition, if customers are not satisfied with their products, they are allowed to return them for a replacement or refund within 30 days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company reduces costs. It allows customers to save as much as 20% off their orders by joining an e-mail list for Zazzle “insiders” that provides exclusive deals. Also, there are no listing fees or monthly/annual fees for designers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company has established a powerful brand due to its success. It bills itself as the world’s top platform for custom products, with over 30 million customers visiting its website monthly. It features hundreds of product lines and over 300 million unique products. It offers designs from over 600,000 professional designers and hundreds of leading brands. These brands include Disney, Warner Bros., Marvel, DC Comics, Coca-Cola, Hallmark, Getty Images, Nickelodeon, and Sesame Street.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;channels&quot;&gt;Channels&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zazzle’s main channel is its website. The company promotes its offerings through its social media pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-relationships&quot;&gt;Customer Relationships&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zazzle’s customer relationship is primarily of a self-service nature. Customers utilize the service through the main platform while having limited interaction with employees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company’s site provides answers to frequently asked questions. That said, there is a personal assistance component in the form of phone and e-mail support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-activities&quot;&gt;Key Activities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zazzle’s business model entails maintaining a common platform between two parties:  consumers and designers. It also involves manufacturing some of its products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-partners&quot;&gt;Key Partners&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zazzle’s key partners are the suppliers that provide it with the equipment and raw materials it needs to run its operations and manufacture some of its products. It also forms partnerships with third-party manufacturers that produce various products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, it operates the Zazzle Associates Program, through which third parties are invited to promote the company on their platforms (websites, mobile apps, etc.). Leads that result in purchases earn the third parties a commission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-resources&quot;&gt;Key Resources&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zazzle’s main resource is its proprietary software platform, which serves over 30 million customers.  It also depends on human resources in the form of manufacturers that produce some of its products and customer service personnel that provide support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It maintains important physical resources in the form of its factory in San Jose, CA. Lastly, as a startup it has relied heavily on funding from investors, raising $46 million from three investors as of October 2007.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;cost-structure&quot;&gt;Cost Structure&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zazzle has a cost-driven structure, aiming to minimize expenses through significant automation and low-price value propositions. Its biggest cost driver is likely transaction expenses, a fixed cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other major drivers are cost of goods sold (a variable cost) and customer support/operations (a fixed cost).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;revenue-streams&quot;&gt;Revenue Streams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zazzle has one revenue stream: revenues it generates from the fees it charges customers for each completed sale.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Businessmodel of Zazzle</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">zalando</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/zalando/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="zalando" /><published>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/zalando</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/zalando/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;businessmodel-of-zalando&quot;&gt;Businessmodel of Zalando&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-segments&quot;&gt;Customer Segments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zalando has a mass market business model, with no significant differentiation between customer segments. It markets its products to men, women, and children. That said, approximately 75% of its customer base is female and most are between ages 25 and 45.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;value-proposition&quot;&gt;Value Proposition&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zalando offers five primary value propositions: accessibility, price, customization, innovation, and brand/status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company gives consumers access to a large selection of products (150,000 each season) from a wide range of brands (over 15,000) that include global, local, and private label offerings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company is able to offer customers low prices due to its operational model. It only orders products from its manufacturer partners after a sale has been completed, enabling it to save on storage, inventory, and logistics expenses. These savings are then passed on to buyers. The company also offers frequent discounts to customers who are registered with its site. The specific section “Zalando Lounge” provides daily notifications of limited-time deals offering savings of up to 75% off the manufacturer’s suggested retail price (MSRP) for top brands. Customers can stay aware of current and upcoming promotions by subscribing to daily and weekly e-mail newsletters. Zalando also offers free delivery and returns with a return policy of up to 100 days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company enables customization by creating country-specific versions of its website and mobile apps. Further, it allows customers to select the type of newsletter they receive via e-mail. They can choose between a daily newsletter featuring all current deals and a weekly newsletter previewing upcoming promotions. They can also tailor their settings in order to turn off newsletter notifications or suspend them for a period of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company fosters innovation by cultivating its in-house expertise. It maintains a team of over 1,000 technology experts, who work in teams to turn new concepts into prototypes that are quickly tested and rolled out into stores for customers to enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company has established a strong brand due to its success, and bills itself as Europe’s top online fashion platform. It serves more than 18 million active shoppers in 15 countries. Its website generates more than 135 million visits a month and had net sales of €3.0 billion in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;channels&quot;&gt;Channels&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zalando’s main channel is its website, through which it acquires most of its customers. That said, it also operates brick-and-mortar stores in Berlin and Frankfurt. The company promotes its offerings through online (search and affiliate) advertising, TV advertising, and its social media pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customer-relationships&quot;&gt;Customer Relationships&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zalando’s customer relationship is primarily of a self-service, automated nature. Customers utilize its website or mobile app while having limited interaction with employees. The company’s site includes a virtual tour of its various sections, a “Size Guide” identifying specific measurements for various categories (Small, Medium, Large) by country, and answers to frequently asked questions. That said, there is a personal assistance component in the form of phone and e-mail support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-activities&quot;&gt;Key Activities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zalando’s business model entails maintaining and updating its platform for its 18 million customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-partners&quot;&gt;Key Partners&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zalando maintains the following key partnerships:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fashion Stylists – The company retains the services of independent fashion stylists who provide personal shopping tips to its customers through an online tool called Zalon. Stylists receive a commission for their advice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Logistics Providers – The company works with a wide variety of logistics companies, including last-mile delivery and long-haul service providers. One of its most prominent partners is PostNord. Zalando also has eight return centers across Europe managed by third-party service providers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marketing Affiliates – The company maintains an online marketing technology platform on its website and app through which third-party brands can advertise their offerings. These brands market Zalando on their sites and apps in return. Both parties earn a commission as a result.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key-resources&quot;&gt;Key Resources&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zalando’s main resource is its proprietary software platform that underlies its website. Its main physical resource is its group of three fulfillment centers, which forms one of the largest online retail footprints in Europe. Its main human resources are its team of 1,000 technology experts across 100 countries who continously come up with innovations, and its team of 400 fashion employees (product managers, buying teams, trend scouts, etc.) who study the industry for the latest trends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;cost-structure&quot;&gt;Cost Structure&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zalando has a cost-driven structure, aiming to minimize expenses through low operating expenses, significant automation, and low-price value propositions. Its biggest cost driver is cost of materials, a variable expense. Other major drivers are in the areas of sales/marketing and distribution, both fixed costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;revenue-streams&quot;&gt;Revenue Streams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zalando has two revenue streams:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Product revenues – The company generates revenues from sales of third-party and private label products on its website and mobile app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Advertising revenues – The company earns a commission from third-party companies who advertise their offerings on its marketing platform (website and mobile app).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Businessmodel of Zalando</summary></entry></feed>